SACHIN UPADHYAY



Software

Developer

CONTACT

(+91) 8209991501

sachinupadhyay2626@gmail.com

https://github.com/Sachin-Upadhyay

n/sachin-

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sachinu-545a6593

https://sachinupadhyay.github.io/SachinWebsite/

EDUCATION

B. tech/Computer Science (Hon.)

MAIET affiliate RTU, Jaipur
2015 -2019

12th Grade/ Science TPS affiliate CBSE, Jaipur 2014 -2015

KEY SKILLS

React Native

Android

Power App, Dataverse

Python

Data Structures and algorithm

Java

C-language

C++ language

JavaScript

OOP's concept

AWARDS

CERTIFICATE

Maggie Marathon, Cloud computing, Organize Engineer's Day etc....

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 4.5+ years of experience in developing mobile applications. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Technossus Software Services Pvt. Ltd /Punjab 06/2022 - Present

- Revitalized Saddleback Church project's graph design with React Native, boosting readability by 25%.
- Developed a Power App that detects criminal record faces, resulting in a significant 50% reduction in processing time.
- Forged an editing tool with PCF (Power App Component Framework) and react for cropping and rotation, yielding a substantial 40% improvement in efficiency.
- Enacted an on-premises data gateway to secure access to local host APIs, elevating security measures by a substantial 30%.

Software Developer

Dotsquares Technologies Pvt ltd /Jaipur, RJ

09/2021 - 05/2022

- Efficiently transitioned from Razor Pay to Paytm, resulting in a notable 20% increase in efficiency.
- Optimized resources and reduce turnaround time by 35%.

React Native Developer

Purgesoft Technologies /Jaipur, RJ

03/2020 - 08/2021

 Elevated the Delivery app by incorporating Mapbox 2.0 for navigation, injecting a dose of efficiency into our streamlined package delivery

Android Developer

Rayqube Future Tech Pvt ltd /Jaipur, RJ

07/2019 - 02/2020

 Scripted unique test plans, test scripts and processes to remove previously known redundancy by 40% and ensured predictable outcomes

Professional Projects

Digital payment with Ecom.

Package delivery app

Employee management

Crypto Buy/Sell

Club membership

Chatting App

Nationality: Indian